http://www.flyingdogales.com/privacy-policy

Beer Finder
Enter Zip Code:
Privacy Policy
Website Privacy Notice Highlights
Welcome to Flying Dog Brewery's online privacy notice (the "Privacy Notice") for this website, www.flyingdogbrewery.com. This website is referred to in this Privacy Notice as the "Site." As used in this Privacy Notice, the terms "you," "your," and "yours" refer to you the user of this Site or any other guest, person, or entity who accesses or uses this Site or services from the Site. The terms "we," "us," "our," “FD” or "ours" refers to Flying Dog Brewery. This notice provides highlights of the full Privacy Notice that currently applies to FD’s collection and use of information from any device used to access or connect to the Site. non-personal identifiable information
Information Use and Sharing
Flying Dog Brewery, LLLP (“FD”) uses information that we gather through the Site to:
Fill product orders;
Process employment applications;
Provide requested information;
Understand how you use the Site so that we can improve it;
Understand more about your browsing behavior so that we can make you aware of our products and our advertising that may interest you;
Improve the content and navigation of the Site, and the products and services that FD provides;
Defend ourselves in the event of law suits; and
Engage in other uses as specified in this Privacy Notice or permitted by law.
Information We Collect and Receive
We collect and receive information about you when you give it to us directly. We also collect information using cookies when you visit the Site. See our full Privacy Notice, below, for further information.
Advertising
We may disclose anonymized information and Non-Personal Information about you for advertising purposes, but not Personal Information, unless we have your permission.
Your Privacy Choices
Unless you opt in, we will not: a. Send you Internet-to-phone short message service (SMS) messages (text messages); b. Send you mobile service commercial messages (MSCMs) directed to one of your wireless devices that you use as the subscriber to a commercial mobile service; c. Send you marketing emails or newsletters; d. Send you any other marketing communications; or f. disclose any Personal Information, other than as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the Personal Information was gathered.
You may opt out of: a. Receiving targeted advertising that is directed to your particular interests, by emailing us at legal@flyingdogbrewery.com; b. Receiving marketing email, by unsubscribing using the appropriate link in a marketing email; c. Receiving telemarketing calls, by telling us to put you on our internal do-not-call list, or for those who have not been our customers for the previous 18 months and who have not given us prior consent to call, by subscribing to the U.S. National Do-Not-Call Registry; d. Our sharing your Personal Information with third parties, by emailing us at legal@flyingdogbrewery.com.
You can manage cookies using browser controls in such a way that some of our data gathering will be eliminated. For more information about how we use cookies, see our Cookie Notice.
Flying Dog Brewery Full Privacy Notice
This Privacy Notice provides information about data we collect, use, and share.
Privacy Notice Overview
What Kinds of Personal Information Do We Collect?
Children’s Privacy
How Do We Collect Information?
How Do We Use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information?
When Do We Share Personal Information and Non-Personal Information?
Browser “Do Not Track” Signals
What Choices Do You Have About Your Personal and Non-Personal Information?
How You Can Correct Inaccuracies
Data Retention
Data Storage and Data Transfers
Links to Other Websites
Security
Contact Us
Privacy Notice Overview
By accessing the Site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Notice. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO SHARE INFORMATION AS CONTEMPLATED IN THIS PRIVACY NOTICE, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE.
This Privacy Notice applies to Personal Information and Non-Personal Information that we obtain through the Site.
When you access or use our Site, you acknowledge that you have read this Notice and understand its contents. Your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use (including any applicable disclaimers of warranties, limitations on damages, and the resolution of disputes).
We may update this Privacy Notice at any time as we deem appropriate. Where the changes are material, we will post them here in advance and, if the changes are likely to affect you personally, we will also attempt to contact you directly (such as via email if we have your email address). It is important that you check back from time to time and make sure that you have reviewed the most current version of this Privacy Notice.
What Kinds of Personal Information Do We Collect?
Personal Information
"Personal Information" refers to information through which you can be identified. We collect Personal Information that you provide voluntarily to us. Some examples of Personal Information that we may collect include your name, date of birth, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, age, gender, and purchase information. If you apply for a job with us, you may be asked for other information, including your employment history. Some Personal Information is considered "Confidential Personal Information." Confidential Personal Information is your name in combination with one or more of the following: credit or debit card number, financial account number, e-mail address, street address, driver's license number, state identification card number, social security number, passport number, and naturalization number.
Non-Personal Information
"Non-Personal Information" refers to information about you or your activities through which you cannot be personally identified. When you use the Internet, your web browser or software may transmit certain information to the servers that host the websites you visit. Such information may include, for example, the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, your geographic location, and your interactions with the Site, including what pages you view and what information you download. When you visit the Site, your Non-Personal Information may be collected. Non-Personal Information may be linked to Personal Information.
Children’s Privacy
If you are under twenty-one (21) years old, do not send any Personal Information about yourself to this Site. In the event that we discover that a person under the age of twenty-one (21) has provided Personal Information, we will immediately delete the person’s information. If you are the parent or guardian of a person under 18 and believe that the person has provided us with Personal Information, you may email us at legal@flyingdogbrewery.com.
How Do We Collect Information?
We collect information directly from you, as well as automatically through your use of our Site.
Information That You Give Us:
Typically, the information we collect directly from you may be to establish a user account, place a product order, request information, or submit an employment application, and usual includes your contact information and other Personal Information. You decide how much information to share with us in most cases, but not sharing required information may limit your ability to obtain services from us. Here are some examples of ways in which you might give information to us through the Site:
Site Registration
You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide Personal Information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password to take advantage of certain features the Site may choose to offer, including but not limited to, newsletters, contests, sweepstakes, forums, message boards or other subscription-based products/services. Your decision to register is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether to disclose information to us and what communications you would like to receive. If you elect not to provide such information, you will not be able to take advantage of those products and services.
Transaction Information
If you order any of the products or services offered on the Site, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including contact information, demographic information and/or financial information. In some instances, we may direct you to a third-party vendor site to collect this information from you directly. Even though the collection form may have the look and feel of www.flyingdogbrewery.com, please be aware you will be giving your information directly to the third-party vendor, and that in some instances such third party vendor's privacy policy will govern the collection of your Personal Information. Please reference the privacy policies available from the third-party vendor’s Web pages for any privacy-related concerns.
We and/or our vendor will use this information to complete the financial or other transaction that you have requested, i.e. to deliver the information, products or other services that you request or purchase, or to invoice you in a manner consistent with this Privacy Notice. For your protection, financial information is collected and stored through encrypted means.
Newsletters and Site Emails
We may offer newsletters to share information with you about the Flying Dog Brewery, or about our affiliates, business partners, advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on the Site. You may cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided on the Site or, in some instances, in the designated area of certain newsletters or emails.
Surveys or Voting
From time-to-time we may request Personal Information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary, and you will have the opportunity to decide whether to disclose information to us through the Site. At times, you may have to register to vote or to take part in a survey.
Employment Applications
You have the opportunity to apply for a job with Flying Dog Brewery through the Site. Your information is gathered for us through a website portal operated by ClearCompany. See below for more information on ClearCompany.
Information Collected Automatically:
We may collect information from you automatically using these technologies:
Cookies
As with many websites, the Site uses a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a collection of information that gets stored on the hard drive of your computer when browsing the Internet. These small bits of code automatically identify your browser to the Site whenever your computer is used to visit the Site. Cookies also let us know how many people visit the Site and where visitors go on the Site. In addition, cookies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like how many times a user has been on certain pages. For registered users, cookies can make using the Site easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Site, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Site are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Site. Cookies may also allow the Site to present to you advertising that may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, your browser should contain an option that allows you to disable or delete cookie data at any time. Some areas of the Site, however, may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our Site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Notice covers the use of cookies by the Site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Here are the specific cookies that we place on your computer if you use the Site:
Necessary
Name
Provider
Purpose
Expiry
Type
csrftoken
flyingdogbrewery.com
google-analytics.com
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
2 Years
HTTP Cookie
_gat
google-analytics.com
Used by Google Analytics to throttle request rate.
Session
HTTP Cookie
_gid
google-analytics.com
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
2 Years
HTTP Cookie
How Do We Use Your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information?
Flying Dog Brewery, LLLP (“FD”) uses information that we gather through the Site to:
Fill product orders;
Process employment applications;
Provide requested information;
Understand how you use the Site so that we can improve it;
Understand more about your browsing behavior so that we can make you aware of our products and our advertising that may interest you;
Improve the content and navigation of the Site, and the products and services that FD provides;
Defend ourselves in the event of law suits; and
Engage in other uses as specified in this Privacy Notice or permitted by law.
When Do We Share Your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information?
We share your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information as is reasonable and necessary to accomplish the purposes described in this Privacy Notice. For example, if you order a mug from our Online Store, we share your Personal Information with the credit card company so that we will be paid for the mug and we share your contact information with the shipping company so that the mug can delivered to you.
Here are some other more specific examples of how we share information:
Online Store. Our online store uses an ecommerce platform provided by www.shopify.com to take orders and process credit card payments. Please see Shopify's privacy notice and terms of use for more information. We currently handle order fulfillment in-house.
Employment Applications. If you submit an employment application to us, you provide the information through ClearCompany’s website portal, and you should consult their privacy notice and terms of use concerning that information as well. Once we get the information from ClearCompany—which is immediately—we just use the information to pursue a potential employment relationship with you, and we get rid of it if you don’t come to work with us.
Contact Us Form Comments About Tap House at BWI. If you write a comment on our send us a message from our Contact Us tab on the Site, and indicate that you are contacting us about “BWI Tap House,” then in addition to routing the message to the top executives of Flying Dog, we also send the message to a company called HMS Host, which operates the BWI Tap House.
Email Communications. We use Mail Chimp to help us manage our email and marketing communications, so we share enough of your information with them to accomplish that purpose. Please see Mail Chimp’s privacy notice and terms of use for more information.
Event Organization. We sometimes gather information from people who are interested in events that we organize. We currently use www.eventbrite.com to do this, and you should see their privacy notice and terms of use for more information.
We do not currently disclose your Personal Information to third-party advertising agencies or advertiser. Some Non-Personal Information about you may be available to others through our use of Google Analytics or other similar analytical tools.
Browser “Do Not Track Signals”
Some web browsers may transmit "do not track" signals to the websites and other online services with which the browser communicates. There is no standard that governs what, if anything, websites should do when they receive these signals. FD currently does not take action in response to these signals. If and when a standard for responding is established, we may revisit our policy on responding to these signals.
What Choices Do You Have About Your Personal and Non-Personal Information?
No Marketing Communications From Us Unless You Opt-In
We don’t send marketing communications to you unless you provide your consent through a sign-up form in the footer of our website.
You Can Always Opt-Out of Marketing Communications
If you wish to opt-out of receiving solicitations from us at any time, you can either opt-out through a link that will be provided in each marketing advertisement or you can email us at legal@flydogbrewery.com.
How You Can Correct Inaccuracies
If you become aware of inaccuracies in your Personal Information that you want to correct or you want to delete your Personal Information from our records, please contact us to let us know, but we reserve the right to retain your Personal Information for our reasonable business or legal purposes.
Data Retention
The time periods for which we retain your Personal Information depend on the purposes for which we use it. FD will keep your Personal Information for as long as we have a reasonable business purpose to do so.
Data Storage and Data Transfers
FD is headquartered in the United States, but uses service providers throughout the United States who in turn may use cloud computing services or cloud storage throughout the world. As such, we and our service providers may transfer your personal information to, or access it in, jurisdictions that may not provide equivalent levels of data protection as your home jurisdiction.
Third-Party Websites
We cannot control the information collection or privacy practices of other websites, including websites operated by third parties. You should review and understand the privacy policies posted on any linked sites you visit before using those sites or providing any Personal Information.
Security
We take what we believe are reasonable security measures to protect the privacy of your Personal Information. However, no security system is impenetrable, and our computer systems could become accessible through a security breach in spite of our precautions.
Contact Us
You may forward any question or concern regarding this Privacy Notice or the use and disclosure of Personal Information to Flying Dog Brewery either by mail or E-mail as follows:
Flying Dog Brewery
ATTN: President
4607 Wedgewood Blvd.
Frederick, Maryland 21703
legal@flyingdogbrewery.com
